brandmovers.co 2016-06-27

# Digital Engagement | Brandmovers | The Engagement Marketers.

**Last updated November 26, 2012.**

Brandmovers, Inc. ("Brandmovers") and its affiliates (Brandmovers India, Brandmovers UK, Brandsurance, Inc.) are committed to protecting users' privacy, and we want to keep you informed of our privacy practices through Brandmovers' Website (the "Website"). This privacy policy (the "Policy") applies to those Brandmovers and affiliate websites that link to this Policy. We encourage you to read this Policy to ensure you understand our privacy practices. Brandmovers reserves the right to update this Policy at any time without notice to you.

Some of our clients provide Brandmovers and its affiliates with personally identifiable information about their customers so we can perform various services such as digital promotions, marketing campaigns, promotion and/or marketing campaign analysis, and other services. Additionally, as part of our services, we may collect information about user interaction with client web sites and we may provide that information, along with any of our other services, to the client, whether in raw form, or in the form of a case study or data analysis. All of this information belongs to the client and, as their customer, you should review the privacy policies of the sites you visit. Brandmovers and its affiliates make no other use of this personally identifiable information, and only collect and use it on behalf of a client.

Please note that whenever it is appropriate to do so, Brandmovers encourages any such clients collecting personally identifiable information to, 1. make you aware that you are providing personally identifiable information to that client; 2. disclose that the provision of such information is subject to the terms of that particular client's privacy policy; and, 3. make that privacy policy available by providing an easily visible link directly to it.

Our services allow our clients to better serve you, their customer. Brandmovers and its affiliates do not presently use cookie technology. If in the future this changes, this Policy will change accordingly to provide users notice and specific information regarding the use of cookie technology.

EMAIL SERVICE ON BEHALF OF BRANDMOVERS OR AFFILIATE CLIENTS

When we conduct an e-mail campaign for our clients, we typically use e-mail service providers. In these instances, we generally do not have access to an e-mail recipient's actual e-mail address or any other personally identifiable information, and if we do we do not associate such data with any person. If we handle the e-mail addresses ourselves in conjunction with a promotion, marketing campaign, or other program, we do not use cookie technology or information for analysis of the promotion, program, or campaign's effectiveness, but rather rely on the e-mail service provider or the client's provided technology to do so.

BRANDMOVERS AND AFFILIATE WEB SITES

The Brandmovers and affiliate websites provide users with information about products and services, as well as company contact information. We do not collect personal information unless you provide it to us for quote requests, proposal requests, or other requests for information. We will express our need for the personal information at the point of collection and will not collect more personal information than is needed to execute your request. This information will be used solely to fulfill your request, and will thereafter be maintained confidentially for our records as proof of your request. This information will never be sold, traded, or otherwise shared with any third parties.

Personal information is any information that can be used to identify an individual, and may include, but is not limited, name, e-mail address, postal or other physical address, telephone number and other information required to provide a service, deliver a product, or carry out a transaction you have requested.

We will only use your personal information in the way we specified when it was collected. We will not subsequently change the way your personal information is used without your consent.

We may respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process by disclosing your personal information and other related information, if necessary. We also may disclose your personal information to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

POLICY UDATES OR CHANGES

Brandmovers and its affiliates may update or change this Policy at any time and such changes will become effective immediately unless otherwise stated. Our Website will state the date it was last updated and we encourage you to review our Policy whenever you use our Website.

We hope you find this information helpful. Our goal is to present all the information in a format that is as readable as possible. Whatever you decide to do, we want you to be completely informed about how we use any collected information.

Should you have any additional questions, please send an e-mail to amitchell@brandmovers.com or write us at:

Privacy Coordinator  
Brandmovers  
590 Means Street  
Suite 250  
Atlanta, GA 30318
